{
  "LevelId": 41,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 419,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "CABBAGED",
      "question": "describe someone who is in a state of confusion, disarray,"
    },
    {
      "id": 420,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "ADOPTING",
      "question": "action involves legally taking on the responsibility for and care of a child or a pet,"
    },
    {
      "id": 421,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BABYSITS",
      "question": "the temporary care and supervision provided by an individual for someone else's child,"
    },
    {
      "id": 422,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BANKCARD",
      "question": "term is commonly used to refer to a plastic card issued by a financial institution,"
    },
    {
      "id": 423,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "ARRESTED",
      "question": "the legal situation when someone is taken into custody by law"
    },
    {
      "id": 424,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "AUTOTYPE",
      "question": "devices that automatically completes or suggests words, phrases,"
    },
    {
      "id": 425,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BACKYARD",
      "question": "the private outdoor area at the rear of a house,"
    },
    {
      "id": 426,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BICYCLER",
      "question": "individual who rides a two-wheeled vehicle"
    },
    {
      "id": 427,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "AUTOPENS",
      "question": "devices are often used to automatically replicate a person's signature,"
    },
    {
      "id": 428,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BAKERIES",
      "question": "sale of various baked goods, such as bread, pastries, cakes, and cookies"
    },
    {
      "id": 429,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BOUTIQUE",
      "question": "describe a small, stylish shop that offers unique and often high-end clothing,"
    },
    {
      "id": 430,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BODYWORK",
      "question": "individuals to engage in physical workouts and activities"
    },
    {
      "id": 431,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "ENTREPRENEUR",
      "question": "individual who starts and operates a business, taking financial risks"
    }
  ]
}